[Dalzollene] At nine tonight,
the mummy of Princess Corco
will be sold off
at the Underground Auction.
Ivlenkov, Tocino, and Baise.
You’ll be responsible for the bidding.
And… The rest of us?
[Dalzollene] Basho and Linssen
will be covering the rear entrance.
Kurapika and Melody
will take the front entrance.
Squala and I will guard the girl.
And so...
the mission will now begin.
[theme song playing]
A x SHOCKING x TRAGEDY
[narrator] It has come to the attention
of the Nostrade family
that someone plans
to attack the Underground Auction
which is put on by the Mafia community.
Kurapika and all of the other bodyguards
hired by the Nostrades
have begun their assignments.
Looks like everyone’s here.
Almost all of them are Mafia bosses.
We’ve got some real heavy hitters here.
[Baise] I'm surprised.
Yeah? Why is that?
Well, this is only an auction.
So, they could have sent proxies
in their place.
Maybe it’s because they feel
like their honor is on the line.
For each winning bid,
five per cent goes back
into the Mafia community.
It’s kind of like a commission.
[Baise] I see. So, in that case…
does it act as a bribe?
Like the more money they bid,
the more they’ll get back in return?
The Mafia has to flex its
financial muscle somehow or other,
and this way is pretty effective.
Oh, I get it.
It’s basically a chance for them
to improve their standing.
Yeah, and as a result,
a few of the gangs
have actually gone bankrupt,
overbidding themselves into oblivion.
It should be starting any minute now.
UNDERGROUND AUCTION
Uh…
I would like to welcome you
to the Underground Auction.
Enough formalities.
Let’s just get down
to the business at hand, shall we?
[all three gasp]
Time for you to die!
[dying groans]
DUAL MACHINE GUN:
AMBIDEXTROUS AUTOMATIC WEAPONS
Get down!
Black Balloons…
Protect us!
ELEVEN ASSISTANTS:
THANKLESS HEROES!
[gasps in shock]
Is he… using Nen bullets?
That means he’s an Emitter, too!
It won’t be long before those bullets
penetrate my Nen barrier
and rip through my body.
Every one of ‘em packs a hell of a punch!
-This isn’t good!
-[dying groans]
Run away!
Go and tell the boss that there--
Go, Baise! I’ll be right behi-- [groans]
[Baise] [terrified exhale]
[cackles]
[Franklin] That was a lot easier
than I thought it would be.
[Feitan] I didn’t get to do anything.
It’s all yours, Shizuku.
Right.
Blinky? Let’s go.
[cackling]
Suck up all traces of the victims
from the room.
Their blood, body parts,
and all of their personal possessions.
Get the chairs, too.
Her Nen ability...
is always fun to watch.
-Hey.
-Hm?
[mafioso groaning in pain]
Someone is still alive.
[mafioso 1] Who--
who the hell are you people, anyway?
[groans]
It doesn’t matter.
You’re all dead, do you hear me?
The community will destroy you for this.
You and your entire family!
They’ll torture you…
they’ll cut you up…
They’ll make you taste hell!
[thud]
Family?
What's that?
[loud gulping]
[Melody] I can’t hear it very clearly,
but there’s a commotion going on
inside the building.
[Kurapika] Something must have happened.
Contact the leader!
I understand.
I’ll call Linssen and Basho, too.
And I want the both of you to head inside.
[mafioso 2] Wait…
What?
[mafioso 3] There’s no one here…
[mafioso 4]
Where did they go? Search the place!
[mafioso 5]
Hey, what happened to the merchandise?!
[mafioso 6]
Get outta here! Head underground, now!
I’m inside,
and it appears that everyone
in the auction house has disappeared.
The whole place is in a state of panic.
It’s completely out of control.
The merchandise.
What about the merchandise?
[Kurapika] Melody is heading
to the underground safe.
[mafioso 7] It-- it’s empty!
[mafioso 8] The goods for today’s auction…
they’ve been stolen!
[mafioso 7] Who could’ve done this?
[mafioso 8] Damn it!
Where the hell did they go?!
[mafioso 9]
Split up and look for ‘em, you idiot!
[mafioso 10] Let’s go!
Get the word out to every family!
And quick!
[Dalzollene] Okay, understood.
We’re going to catch those thieves,
no matter what it takes.
I’m on my way now.
Rendezvous with Linssen and Basho
behind the building.
They’ll meet you in the Central Square.
-Squala.
-Yes, sir.
[Dalzollene] Leave five dogs behind…
just in case.
Right.
[Dalzollene] Listen up!
Don’t take your eyes off the boss!
And don’t let anyone in the room
until we’re back.
[both] Yes, sir.
[mafioso 11] All of the roads are sealed.
The only remaining escape route is by air!
If you see any suspicious aircraft,
contact me immediately.
But make sure not to kill them!
The community has offered a large reward
to the gang that finds the thieves.
Remember!
You have to take them alive!
[Boss] No merchandise?
[Uvogin] None.
In fact, the vault was completely empty.
The auctioneer was the only one
who knew the whole situation,
and according to him,
all of the items were taken
to a new location a few hours ago.
It’s like...
they expected this to happen
and were fully prepared for it.
Oh?
Don’t you think the timing
is just a little too coincidental?
If you wanna know what I think…
we’ve got a Judas among us.
So, you're saying...
that one of us is a traitor?
[Boss] No.
There isn’t a traitor.
And if you ask me...
Judas was nothing of the sort.
It’s said that Judas betrayed Jesus
for 30 pieces of silver.
But to betray all of us…
what would one ask of the Mafia?
Think about it.
What would the traitor gain
by selling us out to them?
Money?
Fame?
Status?
Would that be enough to gratify any of us?
Or to slake our thirst in any way?
[pensive inhale]
Nobody I’ve met is like that, no.
[Boss] Of course not.
And that’s not all that doesn’t add up.
It’s not?
If there was an informant,
the Mafia’s response
was pitifully inadequate.
If they had known beforehand,
that Class-A bounties
would appear at the auction
from out of nowhere,
they certainly would have
bolstered their security.
The guests came unarmed
which tells me no one warned them.
I can’t argue with that.
And that is why I believe...
that while someone did tip them off,
it wasn’t terribly specific.
However...
someone high up in the Mafia community
believed that information.
Okay, I think I follow you.
But I don’t see how this information
is getting from A to B.
Whatever.
So, what do you want us to do now?
When you spoke with the auctioneer,
did you ask where the merchandise
was moved?
[Uvogin] I did,
but he kept insisting he didn’t know,
all the way up until he died.
And Feitan tortured him, so…
He had the worst luck of anyone today.
[Boss] Did you manage to get the names
of anyone who might know?
Do you even have to ask?
The auction is run
by the heads of the Mafia community.
Leaders of gangs in each
of the ten districts around the world.
They’re called... the Ten Dons.
This is the one time of year
that all ten gather in one place
to discuss business and issue orders…
orders which are carried out
by a special force
called the Shadow Beasts.
The team is comprised of combatants
which are hand-picked by each Don.
The best of the best.
Ah, I see.
And since the Shadow Beasts
weren’t called upon
to guard the auction house,
the theory that they
didn’t know we were coming
has even more credibility.
[Uvogin] That does make sense.
[Boss] The question remains:
how did they move the merchandise?
That’s what I’m wondering.
I heard a single Shadow Beast member
turned up at the vault.
The safe itself is 25 square meters
and it was packed full of items
waiting to be auctioned off.
He walked in and then
walked right back out, empty-handed.
The vault was completely bare.
It was a guy in sunglasses
who called himself the Owl.
He must have a Nen Ability
quite similar to Shizuku’s.
[Uvogin] Probably.
But surely,
once 500 people disappeared,
they had to realize…
that they’re dealing with Nen users.
We can take them, can’t we?
[Boss] Of course.
Put on a show for the pursuers.
A disturbance big enough
to draw out the Shadow Beasts.
[Uvogin chuckling excitedly]
I can hardly wait!
[mafioso 12] It’s them!
They’re in a hot air balloon!
[mafioso 13] Looks like It’s headed
for the Gordeau Desert! We're in pursuit!
[leader 1] A hot air balloon?
Not an airship?
[leader 2] That’s impossible!
Then what happened
to the hundreds of guests?
[leader 3] You know I’m starting to think,
maybe we’re not dealing
with an ordinary band
of armed thugs after all…
Huh?
[leader 2] Get the Ten Dons on the phone!
Ask them to dispatch
the Shadow Beasts!
Go!
They’re moving.
Head for the Gordeau Desert.
Okay!
Roger that.
[mafioso 14] Get down here right now
and we’ll even let you decide
whether we drown you or bury you!
[amused laugh]
Just look at the reception
we’re getting, huh?
I’m not gonna have to clean
all this up, am I?
[Feitan] They’re not worth it.
[Uvogin] Hey!
You guys can stay out of this.
I’ll take care of ‘em myself!
[mafioso 15] Wait!
Are you the ones
who kidnapped all of our guests?
Yeah.
Well, you sure have a lot of guts,
I’ll give you that much.
Now which one of you is the leader?
[silly chuckling]
You punk!
[gasps]
[throaty chuckling]
[terrified groan]
[growling]
[roars]
[Nobunaga] His philosophy is simple:
Be stronger than anyone or anything.
Nothing more.
It’d take a heck of a lot more
than an ordinary gun
to leave even a small scratch on him.
[Feitan] Physically, he’s the strongest.
[Franklin] It’s like watching a gorilla
stomping ants.
[Nobunaga] They just keep coming, huh?
Don’t those guys realize
they’re only gonna end up dead?
You know, just watching isn’t much fun.
Does anyone want to play cards?
-I do.
-Count me in.
Look!
I see 'em.
[Uvogin sighs disappointedly]
This won’t even get me warmed up
before the Shadow Beasts get here.
[groans] Ow…
A rifle?
That is so annoying.
Trying to take me out from afar, huh?
[gasps]
[short grunt of pain]
Oh yeah! That was a perfect shot!
[leader 4] That's enough!
Don’t flatter yourself, you monster.
You’re not all that tough.
This super-bazooka is powerful enough
to take out a tank.
I’m about to blow you to bits!
That… hurt my feelings.
See I don’t like being compared
to some measly little tank.
You’re dead!
Did I get him?
-[shocked gulp]
-[gasps]
Well, whaddya know?
That actually kinda hurt.
[terrified shouts]
[derisive snort]
You think I’m gonna let you get away?!
[Kurapika]
It appears that the enemy can use Nen.
And he’s incredibly powerful.
The men who got here first are all dead.
Firearms are useless against him.
That’s impossible…
Take a good look and see for yourself.
His aura’s simply unbelievable.
As is the body count.
It’s insane.
Just what is he, anyway?
Don’t know.
But he’s tearing through all those people
like scraps of paper!
Look, just forget it!
No way I’m trying to capture that!
He’s got a point there.
If we can beat him,
I don’t see how.
-I agree.
-[Squala] Huh?
However, we still have our mission
and we can’t just walk away now.
But still…!
Hold on!
I can’t tell where it’s coming from
but I hear another heartbeat.
[both gasp]
I am the Shadow Beast, Worm.
Which family do you belong to?
[Dalzollene] We’re bodyguards.
We’ve been hired by the Nostrade family.
I understand.
It seems that you can use Nen a bit
but don’t bother.
[Shadow Beast]
These are no ordinary thugs.
To them, killing’s a part
of their daily routine.
You could say
that they’re professional killers.
And as pros ourselves, we’ll handle it.
My name’s Rabid Dog.
And mine is Leech.
You, uh... can call me Porcupine.
Sit back and leave this job
to the Shadow Beasts.
It’s them…
the Shadow Beasts!
[narrator] The Mafia community
has unleashed the dreaded Shadow Beasts
upon the bandits who attacked the auction.
And Kurapika has yet to realize
that these bandits,
they will soon meet in battle
are, in fact... the Phantom Troupe.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Baise!
Her ability’s Instant Lover.
She pretends she’s into a guy,
-then she goes in for a kiss!
-[smack]
So, all you men better be careful!
[both] Smooch!
[Gon] Next time:
"Buildup x to a x Fierce Battle"!
So, uh…
Do bananas count as a snack?
[Killua] What about chocolate?
Is that a snack?
[Gon] Yeah, it’s always been a snack!